TAP version 13
# Subtest: tag edits allow null/empty assignees while retaining team assignment authorization
ok 1 - tag edits allow null/empty assignees while retaining team assignment authorization
  ---
  duration_ms: 72.9409
  type: 'test'
  ...
# Subtest: WABA and phone lists require both owner and company without OR fallback
ok 2 - WABA and phone lists require both owner and company without OR fallback
  ---
  duration_ms: 100.3072
  type: 'test'
  ...
# Subtest: phone filters and team assignments cannot replace contact ownership
ok 3 - phone filters and team assignments cannot replace contact ownership
  ---
  duration_ms: 188.6106
  type: 'test'
  ...
# Subtest: phone access rejects a different owner in the same company and normalizes owned IDs
ok 4 - phone access rejects a different owner in the same company and normalizes owned IDs
  ---
  duration_ms: 45.6207
  type: 'test'
  ...
# Subtest: onboarding cannot transfer another owners WABA or call Meta first
ok 5 - onboarding cannot transfer another owners WABA or call Meta first
  ---
  duration_ms: 101.6674
  type: 'test'
  ...
# Subtest: incoming contacts reuse only the owner, company, and phone identity
ok 6 - incoming contacts reuse only the owner, company, and phone identity
  ---
  duration_ms: 119.7917
  type: 'test'
  ...
# Subtest: local numbers use saved country code and international numbers are preserved
ok 7 - local numbers use saved country code and international numbers are preserved
  ---
  duration_ms: 38.0555
  type: 'test'
  ...
# Subtest: local input matches an already international saved contact
ok 8 - local input matches an already international saved contact
  ---
  duration_ms: 1.106
  type: 'test'
  ...
# Subtest: explicit country code is not replaced and unknown local numbers require context
ok 9 - explicit country code is not replaced and unknown local numbers require context
  ---
  duration_ms: 6.1561
  type: 'test'
  ...
# Subtest: shared national digits across countries require an explicit country prefix
ok 10 - shared national digits across countries require an explicit country prefix
  ---
  duration_ms: 3.4111
  type: 'test'
  ...
# Subtest: campaign creation accepts international digits with or without plus
ok 11 - campaign creation accepts international digits with or without plus
  ---
  duration_ms: 2.1361
  type: 'test'
  ...
# Subtest: campaign creation accepts national numbers with supplied country or saved context
ok 12 - campaign creation accepts national numbers with supplied country or saved context
  ---
  duration_ms: 4.3365
  type: 'test'
  ...
# Subtest: campaign phone payload validation rejects malformed arrays and unsafe numbers
ok 13 - campaign phone payload validation rejects malformed arrays and unsafe numbers
  ---
  duration_ms: 2.0971
  type: 'test'
  ...
# Subtest: incoming profile replaces blank and formatted numeric contact names within account scope
ok 14 - incoming profile replaces blank and formatted numeric contact names within account scope
  ---
  duration_ms: 711.3234
  type: 'test'
  ...
# Subtest: incoming messages preserve saved names and ignore unusable profile names
ok 15 - incoming messages preserve saved names and ignore unusable profile names
  ---
  duration_ms: 312.5548
  type: 'test'
  ...
# Subtest: new unnamed contact falls back to phone and later incoming profile can enrich it
ok 16 - new unnamed contact falls back to phone and later incoming profile can enrich it
  ---
  duration_ms: 58.4716
  type: 'test'
  ...
# Subtest: concurrent contact creation still refreshes placeholder name
ok 17 - concurrent contact creation still refreshes placeholder name
  ---
  duration_ms: 57.5896
  type: 'test'
  ...
# Subtest: latest-message lookup batches full country identities and restricts account and sender scope
ok 18 - latest-message lookup batches full country identities and restricts account and sender scope
  ---
  duration_ms: 224.2505
  type: 'test'
  ...
# Subtest: empty pages and contacts without reliable country or business scope perform no message query
ok 19 - empty pages and contacts without reliable country or business scope perform no message query
  ---
  duration_ms: 128.0833
  type: 'test'
  ...
# Subtest: contact list attaches full message or null while retaining tags and pagination
ok 20 - contact list attaches full message or null while retaining tags and pagination
  ---
  duration_ms: 196.0458
  type: 'test'
  ...
# Subtest: whole-message keywords normalize case and whitespace; unmatched text does not change preference
ok 21 - whole-message keywords normalize case and whitespace; unmatched text does not change preference
  ---
  duration_ms: 127.4142
  type: 'test'
  ...
# Subtest: keyword configuration rejects overlap and malformed lists
ok 22 - keyword configuration rejects overlap and malformed lists
  ---
  duration_ms: 95.2528
  type: 'test'
  ...
# Subtest: incoming STOP and START update only the receiving number/account and campaign guard reads current flag
ok 23 - incoming STOP and START update only the receiving number/account and campaign guard reads current flag
  ---
  duration_ms: 114.3982
  type: 'test'
  ...
# Subtest: malformed stored keyword JSON and non-string entries do not break incoming handling
ok 24 - malformed stored keyword JSON and non-string entries do not break incoming handling
  ---
  duration_ms: 58.2759
  type: 'test'
  ...
# Subtest: settings reads enforce company and owner scope and return consistent defaults
ok 25 - settings reads enforce company and owner scope and return consistent defaults
  ---
  duration_ms: 99.6475
  type: 'test'
  ...
# Subtest: incoming commands reject mismatched receiving scope without changing contacts
ok 26 - incoming commands reject mismatched receiving scope without changing contacts
  ---
  duration_ms: 65.0977
  type: 'test'
  ...
# Subtest: invalid API preference and normalized oversized keyword inputs return validation errors
ok 27 - invalid API preference and normalized oversized keyword inputs return validation errors
  ---
  duration_ms: 45.6014
  type: 'test'
  ...
# Subtest: webhook identifiers split and round-trip through stored fields into Meta recipients
ok 28 - webhook identifiers split and round-trip through stored fields into Meta recipients
  ---
  duration_ms: 33.0431
  type: 'test'
  ...
# Subtest: missing country context never guesses India or another country
ok 29 - missing country context never guesses India or another country
  ---
  duration_ms: 3.9199
  type: 'test'
  ...
# Subtest: same national number under India and US remains two recipients
ok 30 - same national number under India and US remains two recipients
  ---
  duration_ms: 3.6972
  type: 'test'
  ...
# Subtest: incoming lookup includes country, national number, company, owner and business phone
ok 31 - incoming lookup includes country, national number, company, owner and business phone
  ---
  duration_ms: 193.409
  type: 'test'
  ...
# Subtest: preflight reports ambiguous records and only same-scope same-country duplicates
ok 32 - preflight reports ambiguous records and only same-scope same-country duplicates
  ---
  duration_ms: 4.4737
  type: 'test'
  ...
# Subtest: Meta receives international digits and invalid recipients fail before HTTP
ok 33 - Meta receives international digits and invalid recipients fail before HTTP
  ---
  duration_ms: 138.8932
  type: 'test'
  ...
# Subtest: migration stops before data or index changes when clarification is required
ok 34 - migration stops before data or index changes when clarification is required
  ---
  duration_ms: 477.0662
  type: 'test'
  ...
# Subtest: outbound service builds recipients from saved country fields without modifying the contact
ok 35 - outbound service builds recipients from saved country fields without modifying the contact
  ---
  duration_ms: 439.0846
  type: 'test'
  ...
# Subtest: outbound ambiguous or unscoped national recipients fail before message creation and Meta
ok 36 - outbound ambiguous or unscoped national recipients fail before message creation and Meta
  ---
  duration_ms: 268.6558
  type: 'test'
  ...
# Subtest: incoming service persists split sender identity within the receiving company and phone scope
ok 37 - incoming service persists split sender identity within the receiving company and phone scope
  ---
  duration_ms: 104.4613
  type: 'test'
  ...
# Subtest: campaign send rejects a fresh opt-out before message persistence and Meta dispatch
ok 38 - campaign send rejects a fresh opt-out before message persistence and Meta dispatch
  ---
  duration_ms: 92.7089
  type: 'test'
  ...
# Generating preview for file: C:\\Users\\PARTHV~1\\AppData\\Local\\Temp\\validated-preview-VruQmZ\\contacts.csv
# Total rows in file: 6
# Generating preview for file: C:\\Users\\PARTHV~1\\AppData\\Local\\Temp\\validated-preview-VruQmZ\\contacts.csv
# Total rows in file: 6
# Generating preview for file: C:\\Users\\PARTHV~1\\AppData\\Local\\Temp\\validated-preview-VruQmZ\\contacts.csv
# Total rows in file: 2
# Generating preview for file: C:\\Users\\PARTHV~1\\AppData\\Local\\Temp\\country-preview-W3neSK\\contacts.csv
# Total rows in file: 4
# Subtest: detects international codes from the sample without adding default 91
ok 39 - detects international codes from the sample without adding default 91
  ---
  duration_ms: 50.053
  type: 'test'
  ...
# Subtest: national Indian number uses fallback
ok 40 - national Indian number uses fallback
  ---
  duration_ms: 6.0275
  type: 'test'
  ...
# Subtest: explicit international prefix needs no default
ok 41 - explicit international prefix needs no default
  ---
  duration_ms: 1.6961
  type: 'test'
  ...
# Subtest: invalid number is rejected
ok 42 - invalid number is rejected
  ---
  duration_ms: 1.3479
  type: 'test'
  ...
# Subtest: ignores invisible directional marks copied with a number
ok 43 - ignores invisible directional marks copied with a number
  ---
  duration_ms: 5.3386
  type: 'test'
  ...
# Subtest: expands scientific text without changing digits and supports numeric Excel cells
ok 44 - expands scientific text without changing digits and supports numeric Excel cells
  ---
  duration_ms: 5.0531
  type: 'test'
  ...
# Subtest: rejects fractional, unsafe and oversized scientific phone values
ok 45 - rejects fractional, unsafe and oversized scientific phone values
  ---
  duration_ms: 1.3269
  type: 'test'
  ...
# Subtest: Excel import uses raw numeric cells and expands text scientific notation
ok 46 - Excel import uses raw numeric cells and expands text scientific notation
  ---
  duration_ms: 1201.8309
  type: 'test'
  ...
# Subtest: campaign recipients detect international calling codes without an Indian fallback
ok 47 - campaign recipients detect international calling codes without an Indian fallback
  ---
  duration_ms: 4.772
  type: 'test'
  ...
# Subtest: row country codes support numeric, plus, 00 and ISO forms
ok 48 - row country codes support numeric, plus, 00 and ISO forms
  ---
  duration_ms: 10.3131
  type: 'test'
  ...
# Subtest: mixed-country workbook detects each row and never applies 91 to every contact
ok 49 - mixed-country workbook detects each row and never applies 91 to every contact
  ---
  duration_ms: 26.5411
  type: 'test'
  ...
# Subtest: Indian local numbers do not become Myanmar, Maldives, Lebanon or Bhutan numbers
ok 50 - Indian local numbers do not become Myanmar, Maldives, Lebanon or Bhutan numbers
  ---
  duration_ms: 7.0029
  type: 'test'
  ...
# Subtest: import preserves original number in clarification errors without assuming India
ok 51 - import preserves original number in clarification errors without assuming India
  ---
  duration_ms: 20.1262
  type: 'test'
  ...
# Subtest: imports preserve international identities across conflicting optional country hints
ok 52 - imports preserve international identities across conflicting optional country hints
  ---
  duration_ms: 15.5685
  type: 'test'
  ...
# Subtest: CSV with mixed international numbers needs no country column
ok 53 - CSV with mixed international numbers needs no country column
  ---
  duration_ms: 10.9401
  type: 'test'
  ...
# Subtest: validated preview counts all rows and preserves existing sample fields
ok 54 - validated preview counts all rows and preserves existing sample fields
  ---
  duration_ms: 21.6429
  type: 'test'
  ...
# Subtest: Needs country differs from invalid and selected countries resolve local numbers
ok 55 - Needs country differs from invalid and selected countries resolve local numbers
  ---
  duration_ms: 11.5505
  type: 'test'
  ...
# Subtest: resolves timezone and rejects invalid or past one-time dates
ok 56 - resolves timezone and rejects invalid or past one-time dates
  ---
  duration_ms: 111.9422
  type: 'test'
  ...
# Subtest: DST gaps reject and folds choose the earlier instant
ok 57 - DST gaps reject and folds choose the earlier instant
  ---
  duration_ms: 9.3868
  type: 'test'
  ...
# Subtest: yearly preserves wall time, skips non-leap years, and advances strictly
ok 58 - yearly preserves wall time, skips non-leap years, and advances strictly
  ---
  duration_ms: 29.9695
  type: 'test'
  ...
# Subtest: preview renders named and positional variables without recursively substituting values
ok 59 - preview renders named and positional variables without recursively substituting values
  ---
  duration_ms: 11.9427
  type: 'test'
  ...
# Subtest: unsupported template components fail before saving
ok 60 - unsupported template components fail before saving
  ---
  duration_ms: 1.4656
  type: 'test'
  ...
# Subtest: preview returns recipient and sender, enforces ownership and member assignment
ok 61 - preview returns recipient and sender, enforces ownership and member assignment
  ---
  duration_ms: 1324.0362
  type: 'test'
  ...
# Subtest: save rejects opt-out, unapproved templates and mismatched sending number
ok 62 - save rejects opt-out, unapproved templates and mismatched sending number
  ---
  duration_ms: 341.1148
  type: 'test'
  ...
# Subtest: pause/cancel preserve records; sending is immutable; foreign accounts cannot act
ok 63 - pause/cancel preserve records; sending is immutable; foreign accounts cannot act
  ---
  duration_ms: 284.0554
  type: 'test'
  ...
# Subtest: scheduler sends due one-time occurrence once and records its Meta ID
ok 64 - scheduler sends due one-time occurrence once and records its Meta ID
  ---
  duration_ms: 269.4112
  type: 'test'
  ...
# Subtest: yearly send failure is retained and advances to a future occurrence
ok 65 - yearly send failure is retained and advances to a future occurrence
  ---
  duration_ms: 239.4178
  type: 'test'
  ...
# Subtest: opt-out prevents send and stale claims pause without retrying
ok 66 - opt-out prevents send and stale claims pause without retrying
  ---
  duration_ms: 418.9543
  type: 'test'
  ...
# Subtest: campaign mappings resolve contact fields, custom attributes, literals and repeated placeholders
ok 67 - campaign mappings resolve contact fields, custom attributes, literals and repeated placeholders
  ---
  duration_ms: 2.3794
  type: 'test'
  ...
# Subtest: media headers produce Meta payloads and reject malformed URLs and surplus media
ok 68 - media headers produce Meta payloads and reject malformed URLs and surplus media
  ---
  duration_ms: 3.004
  type: 'test'
  ...
# Subtest: reminder preview resolves mappings against current contact and supports image templates
ok 69 - reminder preview resolves mappings against current contact and supports image templates
  ---
  duration_ms: 261.6523
  type: 'test'
  ...
# Subtest: multiple contacts create independent reminders with one shared occurrence
ok 70 - multiple contacts create independent reminders with one shared occurrence
  ---
  duration_ms: 246.4124
  type: 'test'
  ...
# Subtest: invalid or inaccessible bulk contacts leave no partial reminders
ok 71 - invalid or inaccessible bulk contacts leave no partial reminders
  ---
  duration_ms: 230.1431
  type: 'test'
  ...
1..71
# tests 71
# suites 0
# pass 71
# fail 0
# cancelled 0
# skipped 0
# todo 0
# duration_ms 13311.97
